{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293359137}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Ivan is the criminal.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293359575}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293360082}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in red clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293360550}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "Peter owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293361018}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Elena."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293361465}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293361905}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena lives next door from Peter."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293362384}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "Elena owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293362893}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293363370}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Peter is in green clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293363903}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293364357}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293364822}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293365266}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Elena is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293365744}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 also is the criminal.", "Ivan is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 3 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293366195}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293366652}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Peter is at house 1.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293367183}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 2", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293367714}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293368887}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Elena is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat.", "Ivan is at house 2."], "question": "Which is the house of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293370092}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Elena is at house 2.", "Peter is at house 3."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293371304}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293372079}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293372922}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293373793}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter lives 2 doors away from Elena."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293374818}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293375771}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293376718}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293377564}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293378437}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Elena is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a hamster", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293379155}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "Ivan owns a cat."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293380134}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Peter.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Peter owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293381036}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Peter is at house 1.", "Ivan is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293382112}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan.", "Ivan is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293383022}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Ivan is at house 1."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293383800}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Ivan."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293384662}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "Ivan lives next door from Elena."], "question": "Who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293385349}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is in red clothes?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293386315}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293387335}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293388233}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293389051}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Ivan is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293389984}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "Elena is in red clothes."], "question": "Who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293391123}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293392006}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293392975}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan lives 2 doors away from Elena."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293393782}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293394890}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293395865}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in blue clothes.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293396651}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "Peter is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293397561}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 2.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293398971}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "Elena is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293400167}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Peter lives next door from Elena."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293401213}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "Peter is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does Ivan own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293402290}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293403146}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is the criminal.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Elena owns a cat."], "question": "Who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Elena", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293404329}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Peter isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in blue clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293405487}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1729293406435}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Peter is at house 2.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293407200}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293408093}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Peter owns a hamster.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan is in green clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293409209}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is at house 2."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293410397}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter is at house 2.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 3 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293411503}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Elena is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "Elena lives 2 doors away from Ivan."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293412421}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does Ivan own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293413245}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is in green clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is in red clothes also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293414047}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "Peter is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293415032}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Elena isn't the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293415817}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293416590}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "Peter owns a cat."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293417302}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in green clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293418023}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293419087}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in green clothes.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a zebra."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293420283}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "Peter is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in green clothes."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293421263}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "Who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Ivan", "Peter"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293422067}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a hamster."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293422915}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a hamster.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in green clothes.", "Peter is in blue clothes."], "question": "What pet does Ivan own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293423746}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Peter is in blue clothes.", "Ivan is at house 1."], "question": "Who is at house 2?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Ivan", "Elena"], "answer": "Elena", "seed": 1729293424741}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter is at house 2.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes."], "question": "What pet does Ivan own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1729293425747}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293426539}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293427544}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 2.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293428575}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a cat.", "The person who is in blue clothes also is the criminal.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 3", "is at house 1", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293429520}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1.", "Ivan is in red clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 3?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293430781}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Ivan owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293431677}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "Peter is the criminal.", "Peter isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "Which is the house of Ivan?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 1", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293432735}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Ivan is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra."], "question": "Who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["Peter", "Elena", "Ivan"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1729293433698}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293434810}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "The person who is in blue clothes also owns a cat.", "Peter owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in red clothes.", "Peter is at house 1."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 2 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a hamster", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293435946}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in green clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Ivan isn't the person who is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is the criminal is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Elena lives next door from Peter."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293437215}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Ivan is in red clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1729293438349}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Ivan, Peter.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a zebra.", "Peter isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 3", "is at house 2"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293439554}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Elena, Peter.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is is in red clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena is at house 1."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in green clothes", "is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1729293440804}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 3.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a zebra.", "Elena isn't the person who is at house 3."], "question": "What pet does Peter own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1729293442267}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a zebra or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "The person who is the criminal also owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 2 also is the criminal.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What pet does the person who is in blue clothes own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a zebra", "owns a cat"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1729293443978}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "Elena owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 3 also owns a cat.", "Peter lives next door from Ivan.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is in blue clothes."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who is in green clothes?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 1", "seed": 1729293445657}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in red clothes or is in blue clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives 2 doors away from the one who is is in blue clothes.", "Elena is in green clothes.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "Elena owns a zebra."], "question": "Who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1729293446938}
{"facts": ["Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "The person who is is in blue clothes lives next door from the one who is is in green clothes.", "Ivan is at house 2.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of Peter?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in red clothes", "seed": 1729293448029}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is owns a cat lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a hamster."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a cat?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1729293449021}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Elena, Ivan.", "Peter isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is the criminal.", "Peter lives next door from Elena.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a cat."], "question": "What pet does the person who is the criminal own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1730155292337}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Peter, Ivan, Elena.", "Elena isn't the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 3 also is in blue clothes.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "Ivan is in blue clothes.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who is the criminal?", "answer_options": ["is in red clothes", "is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes"], "answer": "is in blue clothes", "seed": 1730155292813}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Elena lives next door from Peter.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a hamster.", "The person who is at house 1 also owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of the person who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["is at house 1", "is at house 2", "is at house 3"], "answer": "is at house 3", "seed": 1730155293219}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a zebra or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in red clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a hamster.", "Peter isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does Elena own?", "answer_options": ["owns a cat", "owns a zebra", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a hamster", "seed": 1730155293646}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a cat or owns a hamster or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in blue clothes or is in green clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who owns a zebra.", "The person who is owns a cat lives next door from the one who is owns a zebra."], "question": "What is the color of the clothes of the person who owns a hamster?", "answer_options": ["is in blue clothes", "is in green clothes", "is in red clothes"], "answer": "is in green clothes", "seed": 1730155294074}
{"facts": ["They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Peter is at house 3.", "Ivan is at house 1."], "question": "Which is the house of Elena?", "answer_options": ["is at house 2", "is at house 3", "is at house 1"], "answer": "is at house 2", "seed": 1730155294517}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a hamster or owns a cat or owns a zebra.", "Any person either is in red clothes or is in blue clothes or is in green clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan is at house 3.", "The person who is in blue clothes is not the person who is the criminal.", "Elena is the criminal.", "The person who is owns a hamster lives 2 doors away from the one who is owns a zebra.", "The person who is at house 2 also is in blue clothes.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a hamster."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a hamster", "owns a cat", "owns a zebra"], "answer": "owns a zebra", "seed": 1730155294965}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a hamster or owns a cat.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Ivan, Peter, Elena.", "Ivan is at house 1.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 2 also owns a hamster."], "question": "Who owns a zebra?", "answer_options": ["Ivan", "Peter", "Elena"], "answer": "Ivan", "seed": 1730155295397}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "Any person either is in green clothes or is in blue clothes or is in red clothes.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "One person is a criminal.", "The person who is is in green clothes lives next door from the one who is is in red clothes.", "The person who is in green clothes also owns a zebra.", "The person who is in red clothes is not the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is in green clothes also is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 1 is not the person who is the criminal.", "The person who is at house 2 is not the person who is in green clothes."], "question": "What pet does the person who is at house 1 own?", "answer_options": ["owns a zebra", "owns a cat", "owns a hamster"], "answer": "owns a cat", "seed": 1730155295828}
{"facts": ["Any person either owns a zebra or owns a cat or owns a hamster.", "They live in 3 adjacent houses.", "People's names are Elena, Peter, Ivan.", "Elena isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is at house 3 is not the person who owns a cat.", "Ivan isn't the person who owns a cat.", "The person who is owns a zebra lives next door from the one who is owns a hamster."], "question": "Who is at house 1?", "answer_options": ["Elena", "Peter", "Ivan"], "answer": "Peter", "seed": 1730155296280}
